





# CONTACT

- 790-254-380
- kubakrawieckk04@gmail.com
- https://github.com/JakubKrawiec2001
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/jakub-krawiec-8b9a6b268

# **ABOUT ME**

I am 22 years old and for almost a year my passion has been creating websites. I am a self-taught person who gained his knowledge through courses on platforms such as Udemy. I consider myself a committed and hard-working person, and working in a team is not a problem for me. Currently I'm studying International Relations at the University of Wrocław. This is my last semester of bachelor studies, after graduation I will start my master's studies at the University of Applied Informatics where I will be able to expand my knowledge of programming, which I can't wait for. I decided to get into programming for a simple reason - it's something I love and it gives me great satisfaction.

## **PROJECTS**

#### 1) Portfolio:

https://jakubkrawiec2001.github.io/Portfolio/

#### 2) FEBU Office:

https://jakubkrawiec2001.github.io/Prywatny-Gabinet-Urologiczny/

#### 3) Movie Searcher:

https://jakubkrawiec2001.github.io/Movie-Searcher/

#### 4) Virtual Keyboard:

https://jakubkrawiec2001.github.io/Virtual-Keyboard/

#### 5)Rock/Paper/Scissors:

https://jakubkrawiec2001.github.io/Rock-Paper-Scissors-Game/

### 6)Pene e Vino Restaurant:

https://jakubkrawiec2001.github.io/Restaurant/

#### 7)MountRide:

https://jakubkrawiec2001.github.io/bike-shop/

## **SKILLS**

- Html
- Css/Sass
- JavaScript
- React
- Bootstrap
- GIT
- GitHub
- Figma
- Hard working
- Engagement
- Group work
- Scrupulousness
- Good organization of work
- Ability to work with the client
- Effective communication

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

1) HRP - Łódź Pomysłów 2019-2020

It was office work. My task was to help clients in obtaining European funds.

2) Diverse clothing store 2022-2023

I dealt with sales and working with the client

# **HOBBY**

- Programming
- Web Development/Design
- Landscape photography
- Computer games/Game Dev

## **LANGUAGES**

English - communicative Polish - native



### **EDUCATION**

University of Wrocław 2020 - currently

International Relations at the Faculty of Social Sciences

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).